[{"answer": "Oh, hi", "docId": "Eternal-Sunshine-of-the-Spotless-Mind.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I think he's in a conference. Unfortunately.  I'm really sorry", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "May I help you", "docId": "Eternal-Sunshine-of-the-Spotless-Mind.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Yes, please have a seat.  He'll be right with you", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " my friend... c'mon..", "docId": "Eternal-Sunshine-of-the-Spotless-Mind.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " It's just...y'know... I mean..", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I'm sorry", "docId": "Eternal-Sunshine-of-the-Spotless-Mind.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Why what", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I'm my friend", "docId": "Eternal-Sunshine-of-the-Spotless-Mind.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I don't know any jokes about your name", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I don't know what that means", "docId": "Eternal-Sunshine-of-the-Spotless-Mind.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I'm nut nuts", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " Yeah.  Although it hardly fits.  I'm a vindictive little bitch, truth be told", "docId": "Eternal-Sunshine-of-the-Spotless-Mind.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " Why wouldn't you think that about me", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Thanks.  That was good, that crow sound", "docId": "Eternal-Sunshine-of-the-Spotless-Mind.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I just thought I'd say hi.  I was in the neighborhood", "docId": "Eternal-Sunshine-of-the-Spotless-Mind.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I was not", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " You didn't say anything about my hair", "docId": "Eternal-Sunshine-of-the-Spotless-Mind.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "In the room", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "It's so cool.  You're by far the most sensational person in the room", "docId": "Eternal-Sunshine-of-the-Spotless-Mind.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "In the world", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "May I help you", "docId": "Eternal-Sunshine-of-the-Spotless-Mind.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Please have a seat.  Dr. my friend will be right with you", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "What?", "docId": "Eternal-Sunshine-of-the-Spotless-Mind.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "my friend, We're fucking gonna talk about it", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "You found us okay", "docId": "Eternal-Sunshine-of-the-Spotless-Mind.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "We haven't checked", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Come up to that place with me", "docId": "Eternal-Sunshine-of-the-Spotless-Mind.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Now.  Now!  I have to go now.  I have to see the frozen my friend!  Now!  Tonight", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "What?  What do you mean", "docId": "Eternal-Sunshine-of-the-Spotless-Mind.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Yes, but... I'm just something you're imagining.  What can I do?  I'm in your head, too", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "There's this guy.  I heard him talking in my apartment.  He's one of the eraser guys.  And he fell for you when they were erasing you, so he introduced himself the next day as if he were a stranger and now you're dating him", "docId": "Eternal-Sunshine-of-the-Spotless-Mind.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "He stole a pair of your panties while you were being erased", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Just shut up, my friend.  I'm going home", "docId": "Eternal-Sunshine-of-the-Spotless-Mind.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I don't want to fight you", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Eternal-Sunshine-of-the-Spotless-Mind.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "God, I should know.  Your hair was red. I remember it matched the wallpaper", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "We did talk about my friend", "docId": "Eternal-Sunshine-of-the-Spotless-Mind.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I'm sure, I said", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "I remember that speech really well", "docId": "Eternal-Sunshine-of-the-Spotless-Mind.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "You had the whole human race pegged", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "This is the night you met my friend, my friend.  I remember watching you walk down the beach with her and I thought, oh shit", "docId": "Eternal-Sunshine-of-the-Spotless-Mind.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I told you that later", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "It was a mutual decision", "docId": "Eternal-Sunshine-of-the-Spotless-Mind.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I didn't make you.  You thought it best.  But, look, I take full responsibility", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "I know.  I had to take the day to think", "docId": "Eternal-Sunshine-of-the-Spotless-Mind.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "I just got in", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "I just walked in", "docId": "Eternal-Sunshine-of-the-Spotless-Mind.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Oddly enough, I do", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Says you were closed off, non communicative, never told me what you were feeling", "docId": "Eternal-Sunshine-of-the-Spotless-Mind.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": " A bully?  my friend", "qsentId": 52}]